Are you seriously
trying to rope-a-dope me?
That's an old man's move.
- I am old man. -No, you're not.
But you box like one.
Not bad.
Come on. Keep your guard up.Come on.
Come on, Ben. You're telegraphin'.
Mr. President.
Ten minutes, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you, Forbes.
Hey.
You're not supposed
to hit the president.
Yeah.l know.
I'll get you next time.
Yeah.I'm sure you will.
Perimeter's secure.
Weather's getting worse out there,
but we're advised it's drivable.
Post vehicles to stand by.
Good evening, Mr. President.
Five minutes, sir.
Thanks, Mike.
- Evening, ma'am.
- Merry Christmas, Mike.
The president gets us off our
dependence on foreign oil...
yet he cannot help
a wife choose an earring.
Uh, small one.
Classic look for a classic lady.
Good chat.
Kiss ass.
Well, I love you both
but I am going with the long.
I hate going to these fundraisers.
Why don't you go for me?
Oh, honey. You're perfect.
God forbid people know we kiss.
Now the real bloodbath starts
when your mom catches you playing this.
You suck.
You suck worse. Come on.
Well,
he likes it when you call him Dries...
because it makes him feel like,
I don't know, you're pals or something.
Hey, love.
You wanna open a gift before we go?
It's not love, and I'm gonna wait
'til everyone else is here.
Keep forgetting. Sorry.
Do I really have to come with you guys?
I mean, I've been on so many.
Re-election's hard work, buddy.
Sorry, pal.
Can I at least ride with Mike?
You'll have to ask him. He's the boss.
Mike, do I get to ride with you?
Okay. All right.
Okay, Diaz.
You're riding in the Beast tonight.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you, sir.
You okay to stay back
and watch the fort tonight?
You kidding me? In this weather?
Get out of this monkey suit,
sit by the fire,
watch "Breaking Bad?" Fine by me.
My own little retirement party?
Leave the babysitter alone, all right?
- Are you going to wear that hat?
- I like the hat.
I think it's fine.
It's age appropriate.
- You take it off when you get inside.
- No, the girls dig it.
Mustang, this is Big Top.
Bringing out the full package.
Let's go.
Package is on the move.
ETA to Morgan residence, 22 minutes.
Keep it tight, everybody.
Hey, Connor. Come on.
Scoot back. Put your belt on.
What if I don't?
Then O'Neil here's gonna punch
in the nuts. Come on.
You keeping 180 degrees awareness?
I thought you said it was 360.
Yeah, I was just checkin'.
Setting me up is what you're doing.
All right. So, how many emergency exits
-in the West Wing? -8.
How many feet from the Oval Office
to the PEOC elevator?
116.
From doors closing in the elevator,
how long does it
take to get to the PEOC?
Four minutes.
Security cameras? How many have audio?
Only the ones in the common areas.
- Not bad. -Kid's got it, huh?
Yeah, we're gonna make
a Secret Service agent outta you yet.
You just need to remember
to keep your seatbelt on.
That's right.
Gosh, it's really coming down.
I've been thinking about shaving my head.
That sounds good.
It's getting worse out there. Bring it down to five.
Merry Christmas, Mr. President.
You shouldn't have.
My God. It's my grandfather's watch.
How did you find this?
Just have my ways.
Thank you.
You're just welcome.
Now, let's talk about that shaved head idea.
You were listening.
You didn't think I was listening,
-did you? -Very clever.
You ever been to a billionaire's
Christmas party before, Diaz?
- No, sir. -They're over-rated.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my gosh.
Look what I found.
Where'd that come from?
Merry Christmas.
Stop, stop, stop!
Hey, Connor, stay right there!
Clear communications, it's Diaz.
- First lady's injured. -Connor.
Get some weight on the back!
O'Neil, get on the back!
I'm gonna get this door!
- Don't anybody move inside! Don't move!
- Mike! Maggie!
- Sir? -Seatbelt's stuck!
Sir, get out of the car!
I'll take care of her!
Keep your weight on the back, O'Neil!
- Hold it back!
- Roma, open the fucking door!
It's jammed! It's fucking jammed!
Pull her out that side!
It's going down!it's going down!
O'Neil, goddamn it!
Hold it down! Hold it down!
- Mike, it's going! -Hold it back!
Mike, take Maggie!
Shit. Sir, I'm sorry!
- Watch out, it's going! -Maggie!
No, Mike!
No!
Mom!
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
And I don't like going to
barbecues by myself, you know?
North Korean maneuvers along the DMZ
continue to ring alarm bells...
throughout Pacific markets,
even as President Asher...
is set to meet this afternoon
with South Korean...
Babe, we out of coffee?
I don't know. Are we?
All right, just...
I thought you said that anything...
You were saying?
I was saying, I'll get some more coffee.
Great.
So, how was the barbecue I missed?
It was actually kind of fun.
You might have enjoyed it.
Yeah?
Paula's got this new boyfriend
who's very sweet...
but he's working in the same department
as her ex, Alex.
Remember Alex?
Anyway,
Alex ended up showing up at the party...
which was really weird for Paula,
who was...
overwhelmed.
Mike, you're not listening to me.
I was listening.
You were talking about
-patty's boyfriend and she's... -No.
Paula and Paula's boyfriend.
You've met Paula.
It's okay, Mike.
We'll talk about it later.
All right, babe. I'm sorry.
But I tell you what.
Why don't we go see a movie tonight?
Okay? Just the two of us.
Or you can bring Paula and Patty
and their boyfriends.
You know what I think we should do?
I think we should take that holiday
that we've been talking about.
All right?
You, me, the ocean.
Come on. It'll be like the honeymoon
we never had.
We didn't have a honeymoon?
Thanks.
So, how was your Fourth?
My fourth what?
Fourth of July. Don't be an ass.
Some people do take holidays, you know.
Yeah, it was quiet.
You know, we stayed in.
We?
Okay. I stayed in. She went out.
I'm shocked.
Ms. Jacobs?
- Good morning. -Director.
- How are you, buddy? -Hey, Roma.
- Good to see you, partner.
- How's the family?
- The kids are good. Thank you. -Yeah.
- O'Neil. -Hey, Banning.
You're looking sharp.
So, we missed you for, poker,
uh, last week. Where were you?
Missed taking your money.
Yeah, I know.
I've been working the late shift.
Yeah, non-stop action over there
at the Treasury.
You gotta do what you gotta do, right?
Yeah.
You guys got a big day coming up, huh?
You got the Koreans coming in?
Nah, I mean, you know.
Business as usual.
Hey, I wanted to introduce you.
This is Agent Jones.
You've heard of Mike Banning,
haven't you?
Yeah, yeah. The guy who told
the Speaker of the House
to go fuck himself.
Don't you guys have somewhere to be?
- Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am. -Yes, ma'am.
- Hey, Mike. Good seein' you.
- Yeah, you too.
- Come Thursday night, all right?
- Okay.
Seven o'clock.
Not getting any easier, huh?
No.
I want back in.
Desk job's killing me.
Mike.
Everybody knows you did the right thing
on that bridge.
Hell, even the president knows.
He just doesn't want to see you
and have to be reminded of it every day.
He never even stopped
to grieve properly.
Just, give it some time.
How's Connor?
President's son, misses his mom.
Hell of a gig.
Misses his buddy though.
Yeah, he's a good kid.
Is he still sneaking
around the White House,
making everybody crazy?
Oh, I wonder who taught him that.
You know, the first time you walked
into my office out of the darkness...
you needed therapy then.
Never mind now.
And you don't exactly
do yourself any favors.
Where are you going with this?
Mike. Look, you gotta learn
how to get back into the real world.
That's good, Jacobs.
Let me write that one down.
Hey, Jacobs.
Thanks.
I'll be in touch.
Hey, buddy. What do you think of this?
- Which one do you like? -I don't know.
Okay, you take that one.
I'll take this one.
- Maggie! Maggie!
- I'll take care of her!Sir!
No! No, Mike!
Mr. Foss came in. Chest pains.
About an hour ago.
Hey, it's Leah.
You've reached my phone.
You know what to do.
Just checking in.
Listen, I'll call you later. Bye.
Get some fishing in.
Hit the bag together. Be fun.
I hate Camp David.
Do we really have to go?
Can't we go somewhere else?
You know, the beach?
Yeah.
The beach does kinda sound better.
Hey.
I've got three minutes.
Let's run down to the kitchen
and get some ice cream.
Yeah.
Chocolate chip or rocky road?
I'm gonna have rocky road
before you eat it all,
like you did the last time.
- I don't remember it that way.
- Yeah, you did.
Come in.
Mr. President, we're ready for you.
- Already? -Yes, sir.
Sorry, buddy.
It's okay, Dad.
All right.
I'll see you soon.
Minister Lee
is going to want you to issue
a joint statement, Mr. President...
threatening military action
to get the North Koreans...
to stand down from the border
and stop their missile tests.
Which I think we should give them.
Ruth?
Provided that the
North Koreans are rational...
which is dicey, at best.
We bluff. They call it. Then what?
Well, who says we'd be bluffing?
Personally,
I like to try to avoid a war.
Charlie?
I think I agree with Ruth on this one,
Mr. President.
Thank you for sitting in, Mr. Speaker.
- Yes, sir.
- I won't hold you up any longer.
- Hello, Mr. Speaker. -Hello, Janie.
What time is Minister Lee due to arrive?
7:00 this evening.
Our guests have arrived.
Prime Minister Lee.
I'm Special Agent-in-Charge Roma.
I'd like to welcome you
to the White House, sir.
Thank you.
May I introduce my Head of Security
and Chief Aide, Mr. Park.
My pleasure.
Prime Minister, after you, please.
Agent Davis will be taking care
of your security team outside.
Prime Minister, if you would follow
Agent O'Neil, please?
Ma.
am?
Private sector looks good on you, Dave.
Yeah, something to look forward to.
Yeah. How've you been?
I'll tell you.
I miss the Secret Service.
Best years of my life.
It misses you too, old man.
I could still kick your ass.
At what? Dominos?
-It's good to see you, my friend.
- You, too.
Unidentified flight,
this is Flight Leader, U.S. Air
Force aircraft at your starboard wing.
You've entered restricted airspace.
Unidentified flight,
you must divert immediately
to vector 0-2-0. Acknowledge.
I'm sorry to have
disrupted your vacation.
Please. I'm glad you could come.
Mr. Lee, we have a mutual problem.
And I think together,
I'm confident we can find a solution.
Thank you, Mr. President.
That's why I'm here.
As you know, North Korea
has a one million man standing army...
less than 50 kilometers
from our capital.
The threat is real.
Unidentified flight.
You must divert immediately
to vector 0-2-0.
This is your final warning.
You will be shot down. Acknowledge.
Anti-aircraft. We're taking fire.
Mr. Lee, I'm sure you can appreciate
that this is...
Sir? There's been an incursion.
Please stand up.
Let's go. Move!
- Mr. Lee, please join us.
- That's not protocol, sir.
He's coming with us!
Move, move, move!
Get him to the elevator.
- Go!Go! -Find Connor!
Code 9-9-9.
Go. go, go! Move!
Keep moving!
Get that elevator open now!
Give me four minutes, Mr. President.
Harden down on Olympus.
Air support on the way.
ETA, four minutes.
Code Red. Air space 1 and 2 compromised.
Robert, Delta, Ready One.
Move to West Corridor!
This way, please.
This is not a drill.
Evacuate immediately.
All units, 9-9-9.
I repeat, all units, 9-9-9.
Let's move!
Find my son.
Sylvio, find Sparkplug immediately.
You okay, Mr. President?
Sir. This way. Over here.
Go on! Get down!
Get down!
Stay down! Don't move!
Get down! Get out of the way!
Take cover!
PPD Command, this is Wolfhound 6.
Have bogey in sight.
Wolfhound 6, fire at will.
Repeat, fire at will.
Acknowledge.
Mr. President?
We have confirmation
that the bogey is down, sir.
Thank you, Jones.
Activate Compound One.
I want open lines to the Pentagon,
Homeland Security and NSA.
Charlie.
Coordinate with the Air Force and FAA.
- Find out if that's' a lone aircraft.
- Yes, sir.
Half hour at the most.
Ruth. Where the hell is my son?
Hey!
Hey, get the fuck down!
Mr. Lee. We've had a problem.
- Please have patience with us. -Got it.
- Mr. President. -Yes?
It's a critical message.
The White House is under ground attack.
Officer on deck!
Rapid Response Team from Andrews,
get 'em moving!
At ease. How bad is it?
Front fence has been breached.
We've got a C-130 burning
on the South Lawn
and a gunfight raging on the North.
Fucking shitting me.
Where's the president?
In the bunker.
- Get me the Pentagon on the line now!
- Yes, sir!
It's happening.
Mr. President!
Forbes, what are you doing?
- Move! -For God's sakes, Forbes.
Forbes! What are you doing?
Shut up!
Come on. Tim.
Come on. Hang in there!
Hey!
Ah, shit.
Where's the president?
I don't know!
Goddamn it! Where's that response team?
- They're 5 minutes out, sir, but...
- But what?
We have a hostage situation
on our hands.
P.E.O.C.'s gone offline.
Go back! Get back now! Go back!
Fuck!
RPG!
Get in! Get inside! Get inside!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Go, go! Move!
Fall back, fall back!
Let's go, let's go!
- They're down the hall!
- Shit, we've only got four guys left!
Hold your positions, you understand?
I got this door. Cover the other one.
Olympus has fallen. Olympus has fallen.
Olympus has fallen.
Fuck you!
They've taken the White House.
Command, Sniper Team One, in position.
We're coming from the White House.
So far, the perimeter's been set.
We're waiting on more intel to come
in right now, and once we do...
Bravo team's gonna breach.
- Wait for my command to execute.
- Yes, sir.
Not since the British burned down
the White House in the War of 1812...
has an enemy force occupied
the center of American power.
The White House,
the most protected building on Earth,
has fallen.
Sir,
we have a hot feed from the P.E.O.C.
Mr. Lee. Sir, are you safe?
Are you with the president?
Sir, can you hear m...?
Oh, my God.
Don't negotiate.
Sir?
I have your commander-in-chief.
Now, stand down.
Who are you?
I am the man in control
of your White House.
Now, stand your men down.
- Stand down! -Sir.
All units, stand down!
Ladies and gentlemen we are at DEFCON 4.
How could you?
- Put your hands up. -Fuck you.
No!
There is a reason I never voted for you.
Don't do it, Forbes!
It takes 15 minutes
for your Armed Forces
to reach the White House.
We took it down in 13.
Hurry, we need a wheelchair.
In Triage, do you want me
to color code them or number code them?
Color code 'em.
Okay, Pam,
we still need to take the vitals.
Call, Mike. Mike.
The cellular service in the area
you are calling
has been suspended temporarily.
I got head trauma,
six-year-old girl, she's fading!
Bring Mr. Asher here.
What are you doing, for Christ's sake?
Oh, sir!
I have no interest
in your nuclear launch codes.
By now your Pentagon
has changed then, no?
Sit.
You from the North?
You sure as hell are not from the South.
I'm working for justice.
To give millions of starving
men, women and children
a chance at more than just subsistence.
To end the civil war your country
interrupted so long ago.
And yes...
for a united, prosperous Korea.
It's a whole new world, baby.
What's the going rate for souls
these days?
What'd you say to me?
I never would have taken you
for a traitor.
Me?
What about you?
You sold this country out long
before I ever did.
Globalization and fucking Wall Street.
What's it cost to buy
a presidency nowadays anyway?
$500 million?
I'm a fucking rookie compared to you!
Gotta keep your gloves up, Forbes.
Enough!
What about Connor?
What the fuck are you gonna do
with my son?
Mr. Speaker.
As both the President
and the Vice President
of the United States
are unable to discharge
the duties of their offices
I'm officially placing you
under Secret Service protection.
You are the Acting President
of the United States.
Are they alive?
They are.
Sir, North Korea is denying
any involvement in the attack.
We've secured the perimeter
of the White House...
and cleared a 10-block radius.
Sir, they've also assassinated
the South Korean Prime Minister.
We have contact
from inside the White House.
Trace confirms
it's the president's Sat phone.
Put it through!
Mr. President?
Negative.
-Identify yourself. -Echelon Four.
That's one of yours?
- Designator? -Oscar Zulu 309.
Jesus. Banning? Where are you?
I'm in the Oval Office.
Is the president in the bunker?
- He... -Can we trust him?
Banning was one of our best agents.
Mr. Speaker, I just have to say,
this is Mike Banning.
This is the same guy that was removed
from the president's detail...
-after the accident -Whoa, whoa,
-when we lost the first lady?
- Ray! Ray! Ray!
- You wanna add something?
- Well, what's he doing
- I suggest you get your facts straight.
-In the White House right now?
- How do we know we can trust this guy?
Banning is ex-Special Forces,
Ranger Battalion
He will move mountains or die trying.
I know him.
Does anyone else in this room
have any intelligence
coming out of the White House?
Then we have no choice.
Yes. The president's in the bunker.
He's being held hostage.
What do they want?
We're trying to find out.
Who's in charge?
Trumbull.
- Are there any survivors with you?
- Negative, sir.
They wiped us out.
They have commandos roaming
the hallways...
with enough explosives
to take out an army.
Looks like the doors and windows
are rigged with C-4 explosives.
Who knows what other tricks
they have up their sleeves?
Any team coming in is gonna be ringing
the front doorbell pretty loud.
They shut the power down.
Lights off.
And I assume they closed the air vents.
I killed the surveillance,
but I don't know
how long that's gonna last.
Where's Connor?
Oh, we have no status of his location,
but he's presumed to still be inside.
Well, they're looking for him.
They have his photo.
Sir...
I'm here. Use me.
Okay, Banning. Sit tight.
We'll get back with you.
Sir, we have a hot feed
from the P.E.O.C.
- Mr. Speaker. -What is it you want?
Recall the Seventh Fleet
from the Sea of Japan.
And withdraw all 28,500 American troops
from the Demilitarized Zone.
If you do not comply.
If you attempt any operation
to take this building...
-if you deviate from my instructions...
- Wait a minute.
We can't just recall the Seventh Fleet.
Then I will execute your officials
one by one...
and their blood will be on your hands.
You have until dawn.
I suggest you move quickly.
Who is that guy?
Well, sir, we're running facial
recognition on him right now.
Well, he cleared as part of
the South Korean security detail.
If we recall the Fleet,
and leave the DMZ...
Seoul, all of South Korea could fall
within 72 hours, sir.
But if we do nothing, they kill Asher,
the vice president...
and his entire National Security team.
And Connor, if he's in there.
Mary, get me some coffee
Half-and-half, three Sweet 'N Lows.
In a real cup.
Not one of those paper
or Styrofoam things.
All right.
Let's secure all nuclear sites.
Get me our expert on North Korea.
Then I want to speak with the Premiere
of North Korea on a secure line.
After that,
I wanna speak with the Russians,
the Chinese,
the British and the French.
And set up a press conference.
In that order.
The United States of America
doesn't negotiate with terrorists.
Who said anything about negotiating?
Admiral Hoenig, your Cerberus code.
You kill him, you won't get the code.
I will not ask again.
- Give it to him, Joe. -Mr. President.
You'll never get mine.
Tango-Juliet-1-9-3-3-4.
Louder.
What the hell?
Get me Homeland Security.
No, now!
Sir. NORAD reports a Cerberus code
has been entered.
Jesus.
Jacobs, I got something coming your way.
I got a clean commando in front of me.
- What is that? -Is he alive?
Ask me a serious question.
Anybody around the table?
We don't recognize it.
Well, whoever they are,
they're fucking good.
They're well-trained
and they're well-organized.
But I guess you know that already.
Get that over to Langley.
So, what have you got? Talk to me.
They want us to recall the Seventh Fleet
and pull our troops out.
Oh, is that all?
A Cerberus code has been entered.
What's Cerberus?
That's classified.
Classified? Really?
Well, right now I think I have
the proverbial need-to-fucking-know.
Cerberus is a
highly-classified military protocol.
A 3-pronged fail-safe in the case of
an inadvertent nuclear launch.
It allows us to access
the self-destruct mechanism
in our lCBM's in-flight.
So even if one of our nuclear warheads
was launched and we wanted to abort.
Cerberus is the only way to stop it
from reaching its target.
No one person has all three codes.
It's parceled out to the president,
Secretary of Defense...
and the Chairman of the Joint Chiefs.
All of whom are
in the president's bunker right now.
With those codes, they can destroy
any long-range nuke that we fire.
And that would make America vulnerable
to a nuclear strike.
So, change the codes.
We can't.
Cerberus was designed
as a self-contained
total-isolation system.
The only way tochange the codes
is physically on the computer itself.
Which is located
in the president's bunker.
So, now we know why
they wanted the president's son.
The president will hold out
as long as he can.
But if they get his son...
if they hurt him...
well...
nobody could hold out
under those circumstances.
So, find Connor
get him the hell out of there.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Forbes.
Who is that?
Mike Banning.
And who might that be?
He was on the president's protection
detail for a few years.
Are we worried about him?
Hell no.
No.
He should be.
Did Truman gut the White House interior
in 1948 or '49?
I believe it was '49.
Steel frame over
the old stone walls. Yes?
Connor!
- How're you doing? Okay?
- Yeah, I'm all right.
I see this is still
your favorite hiding place, huh?
I've got Sparkphlg-
Finally, some good news.
He's safe. I'm bringing him out.
What about my dad?
Your dad's gonna be fine, okay?
Nothing bad's gonna happen.
We're gonna get him outta here.
- Okay? -Yeah.
All right. Let's get outta here.
- You ready to haul ass? -Yeah.
Okay, stay close.
Okay.
Come on.
Okay, come on.
All right, kiddo.
Keep an eye out, okay? Watch my six.
Jacobs.
Okay, I have Sparkplug.
He's coming out in a ventilation shaft
in the northwest corner, ground floor.
Have the green party waiting.
We'll be there.
How are you gonna fit through that?
You're coming with me, right?
I gotta go get your dad.
All right. Now, listen, you can do this.
Now, you remember chimney climbing
I taught you on the Rose Garden wall?
Yeah? So, that's all it is. Okay?
It's one foot against the front wall,
one foot against the back.
Now, all the way to the top.
- Mike? -Yeah.
I'm scared.
Yeah, me too.
But you're gonna get through it.
You're one of us now.
This is yours. Put that on.
Now, I'm counting on you, kiddo.
Okay.
Good man. All right. Let's go.
There you go, kiddo.
I'm gonna push you on up, okay?
I'll see you on the other side.
Now, keep movin'.
Sparkplug is on his way up.
Oh, Jacobs, hold on. Connor, wait up.
- False alarm. Go. -Okay.
He's coming out, Jacobs.
Hold your position.
Hostiles in the area.
Go, go, go! It's clear.
CIB-1. Going in.
You Okay?
Coming out.
Hostile moving toward the ledge.
Hustle up.
Sparkplug received.
Good job, Banning.
Now, let's see
if we can get the president out.
Roger that.
I want to reassure all Americans
and everyone around the world
that despite today's events
our government remains 100% functional.
We know that the president is alive.
To our friends, we are grateful
for your loyalty and support.
As a nation,
we are never stronger than when tested.
We will remain united and strong.
God bless you all
and God bless
these United States of America.
Okay, asshole.
Yo. Hey. Who's running the show?
Oh, you speak English?
They teach you that where you come from?
'Cause you know what they teach me?
Is how to extract information
from people like you.
That's funny, huh?
No, it's funny. I know. I get it.
Yeah. I guess I'm a little rusty.
I liked your friend though.
He seems like a funny guy.
What's your leader's name?
Oh, I'm sorry. Here.
How many men do you have?
In English.
His name is Yeonsak Kang.
He's the head of the KUF.
The paramilitary organization?
No surprises there.
40 commandos breached the gate
and 28 are left.
How do we know
we can trust the information?
I just asked them nicely.
Kang Yeonsak?
Sir, this is one of the most
wanted terrorists in the world.
He was brought across the DMZ as a child
after his father was executed
for crimes against
the North Korean state.
While they were crossing the border,
his mother was killed
by an American landmine.
This guy masterminded the 2004 bombing
of the British Embassy in Seoul.
And he funneled Pyongyang uranium
enrichment technology from Pakistan.
He's never before been
photographed or identified
by any Western intelligence agency.
Well, Jesus Christ,
nobody ever thought to look for him
inside the South Korean government.
Look, I don't care who he is.
With a force that size
I have men who can sweep 'em out
in short order.
Sir, this is not going to be a cakewalk.
These sons of bitches
are pretty fucking tough.
I've got the toughest fuckin' guys
in the world.
What we need to know is
how to get into that bunker.
Once those blast doors close, you don't.
It's nuclear hardened.
Now, there used to be some old tunnels,
but they were sealed up years ago.
Sir, your men need to know
what the hell they're dropping into.
Do not launch anything
until I do some recon.
Agent Banning. Yes, I know who you are.
Welcome to my house.
Hey, asshole. What took you so long?
You're the one that
let the first lady die, no?
And soon, the president.
Failure seems to be a habit with you.
Yeah, well...
Maybe I owe you for giving me the chance
for making up for that today.
I admire you
for acknowledging your failure.
But there's no going back.
Nothing you try and do here
tonight can atone.
Yeah, maybe not.
But I reckon fucking your shit up
will be a pretty good start.
You may wanna take a headcount.
The bodies are piling up.
I have more than enough men
to finish the mission.
Oh, and by the way,
if you're looking for Connor...
he's on his way to the baseball game.
How's your wife, Michael?
Leah. She's a nurse.
Saves lives.
Too bad she will not save yours.
You know what?
Why don't you and I
play a game of fuck off?
You go first.
Go kill him.
Enough!
Madam Secretary.
Your Cerberus code.
No!
Ruth!
Your code!
You'll have to kill me.
As you wish.
There's a saying...
in Korea.
Seeing something a 100 times...
is not as good as living it once.
Fuck you.
Stop!
Enough!
Enough! Stop!
Give it to him, Ruth.
It doesn't matter.
And he won't get mine.
Ruth.
Give it to him!
That's an order, Ruth.
Sir...
Give it him, Ruth.
Yes, sir.
Echo-Mike...
6-0-2-8...
5, sir.
Get your fucking hands off of me!
Sir, NORAD reports that the second
Cerberus code has been entered.
My God.
- Mike! Mike, Mike, it's me. -Dave?
You scared the shit out of me.
Jesus, what the fuck?
Yeah, just put that thing down.
I almost blew your
fucking brains out, man.
What are you doing here?
I was with the South Korean delegation.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I thought you were working
at the Treasury.
Yeah, I am.
Believe it or not,
I came in through the front door.
Oh, fuck, Mike.
I saw my life flash in front of me.
Look at my hand. Fucker's shakin'.
Jesus Christ.
It's good to see you, buddy.
You got a funny way of showing it.
Is the president okay?
He's alive for now.
They got him in the bunker.
It's a fucking shit show, huh?
Yeah, that's for sure.
Roma make it?
Fuck.
We gotta keep movin'.
- You got a plan, Mike? -Yeah.
But it hasn't worked out so far.
Fuckin' Mike. You always were a hardass.
You never change.
Hey, Dave.
This place is getting me rattled, man.
I can't think straight.
You Okay?
No. Not for real.
This fucking Kang, man. He's crazy.
How do you know his name?
Hey, Mike, do you remember that time
in New York?
Dave.
Why'd you do it?
Fuck, Mike.
Fuck.
I lost my way.
You can make up for it now.
Tell Kang I'm dead.
You'll help me save the president.
Kang. It's Forbes.
I got him. All clear.
Good.
Ruth.
Mr. President, sir?
Rough day.
Could be worse.
How's my hair?
Not a strand out of place.
Any regrets?
None.
YOU?
A few.
Like running for president.
The office is lucky to have you, sir.
We all may meet our maker today...
but the one thing
I do not want on my tombstone...
"She Went Down Without a Fight."
No danger of that.
Pull up your satellite feed.
Give me eyes on.
Looks like there's only four sentries
on the roof.
With the Air Defense grid gone,
they're vulnerable
to an aerial insertion.
Wait. Let me get there first
and check it out.
We're not waiting.
We have to secure Cerberus.
Oh, fuck.
Send in the SEALS, General.
We're going through the roof.
Command, Tiger Flight inbound.
Tiger Team, stand by.
The assault team is on the way.
About fucking time.
Yes, sir. Copy.
Command,
Tiger Flight's three minutes out.
Team, go green.
Go green.
Cho.
60 seconds to target.
I want a clean deployment.
Fuck.
Tell them to hold.
We aren't holding shit!
Jacobs. You've gotta abort his mission.
They've got the Hydra Six!
What's that?
Next generation weaponry. Ours.
How the hell would they get that?
It doesn't matter. We'll take it out.
I said abort this fucking mission!
Let's go get our goddamn house back,
Captain.
Tiger Two, Tiger Three,
you're cleared hot.
Tiger Two, roger.
Tiger Three, roger.
All birds, be on the lookout
for possible advanced weaponry.
Approaching rooftop.
Negative on the four sentries.
Tiger Flight's on station.
We got 'em.
Go, go, go!
Fast ropes deployed.
We have a radar locked sourced
from target.
Tiger Two's taking fire
from the rooftop!
Tiger Team, go combat flight.
Tiger Two's hit.He's going down.
Tiger Two going down hard.
Tiger Two's hit.
Evasive, evasive.
Take out that target.
Concentrate fire on that rooftop.
Tiger Three, fly behind the target.
Tiger Four, adjust approach!
Head northwest and flank from there!
Tiger Five and Six, switch to Formation
Charlie and take out that gun!
Damn it, drop altitude!
Tiger One gunner just got hit!
Watch your three. Watch your three.
Taking fire.
- Hold on! -We're getting hit!
Tiger Six is down!
Tiger Five taking...
Tiger Five's gone down.
Reset formation. Tiger One taking lead.
Roger that.
We need backup!
They're chewing us up!
Engaging Target. Provide cover.
All remaining Blackhawks,
provide air cover.
Two birds up. Only two birds remain.
Abort! Abort!
Pull out. Clear the area.
Roger! Clearing the area!
Tiger One is hit! Losing control!
Tail rotor failure.
Mayday, mayday! We're going down!
Five out of six birds are down.
Requesting QRT.
Permission to launch second squadron.
Negative, negative.
We don't have any intel about
what other surprises
they could have for us.
Return to base. Return to base. Over.
Roger that.
Banning, are you there? Banning!
Half the White House is just gone.
The residence, the roof,
all destroyed...
and the remainder of
the historic building now trashed.
Speaker Trumbull,
that was a very foolish undertaking.
Your president is next.
You now have one hour
to recall the Seventh Fleet
and your troops.
Once you do so,
I want a helicopter on the North Lawn
fueled and ready.
60 minutes.
Fuck.
It's Banning.
Patch him through.
- Mike? -Yeah.
We've been trying to reach you, son.
Are you okay?
Mr. Speaker, sir,
if we ever get out of this shit storm...
you can hold me for insubordination.
But your team needs
some serious fucking help.
This is General Clegg,
Army Chief of Staff.
I am ordering you to stand down.
Remove your only eyes and ears
from the ground.
That's fucking brilliant.
We need to pull you out of there
before we lose another hostage!
I am giving you a direct order.
Newsflash, asshole.
I don't work for you.
General Clegg.
I'm the Commander-in-Chief.
If I didn't absolutely need you,
I would relieve you right now.
I will not let this asshole
- General.
- Blow up America, sir!
- I don't wanna here another word...
out of you unless I ask you a question!
Sir.
Mr. Banning.
Mr. Banning, are you there?
Yes, sir. What's the plan?
We're recalling the Seventh Fleet
pulling our troops back from the DMZ
and giving them the helicopter.
Sir, you cannot do that.
You cannot give this guy what he wants.
I've dealt with
these types of men before.
Give me some time. Let me flush him out.
We are talking about the safety
of the President of the United States!
We're talking about a hell of
a lot more than that, sir.
With all due respect,
you're acting president now.
And I'm the best hope you've got.
Okay, Mike.You've got 30 minutes.
Leah, call for you on the landline.
The emergency line.
Can you make sure he gets some morphine?
Yes.
Mike?
Hey. I was just checking in.
Babe. How's your day been?
Yeah, it's been busy.
It's good, you know.
How 'bout you?
Yeah.Busy.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, I just, I've, I've had to stay
a little later than I expected.
Yeah, me too.
You're gonna come home tonight, right?
Yeah. Sure.
We got a date, remember?
Hey, I gotta go.
You know, this, uh,
paperwork's piling up.
Okay.
I love you.
What's the matter, Kang?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
I guess you don't know
who you can trust, huh?
It's over.
No more televised executions.
No chopper.
No more negotiating with you
and the United People's Front
of Who Gives a Fuck.
I will send the president out...
one piece at a time.
It won't matter.
Because whatever you think
you accomplished
you won't be alive to see it.
Shut him down.
Ah, you're not shutting me down, Kang.
I'm here to stay.
I underestimated you.
It will not happen again.
There is no again.
You're gonna die down there alone
cut off from the rest of the world.
My advice?
Save the last bullet for yourself.
'Cause if you don't...
I'm gonna stick my knife
through your brain.
But don't worry.
I'm gonna leak the photos
of your body to the press.
You know, 'cause I know you
like that kind of shit.
Her!
I pledge allegiance to the flag...
of the United States of America!
Your leader is out of his mind.
You fucking idiot!
Go.
Walk.
Move!
Sir, there's movement
in front of the White House.
Ours or theirs?
Looks like Secretary McMillan, sir.
- Any bulges, wires? -Negative.
Sir, ground reports activity
at the White House.
- Is that? -McMillan.
Get a team out there now.
And another to cover! Go!
It looks like Secretary McMillan.
Yeah, yes, it is.
Yes!
Mike?
Hey.
He got away. He's back in the bunker.
You gave it a good shot, Mike.
You saved McMillan.
North and South Korean military
forces are onhigh alert
in response to rumors
of an impending American
pull-out from the DMZ.
India, China and Russia
have declared a state of emergency
and have mobilized military forces.
In the Middle East though,
the response to the attack
on the White House is jubilant.
Crowds of thousands
are celebrating in the streets
and American flags are burning.
...created by a U.S. departure
could spark
an immediate and full-scale conflict
and that any conventional war
in this heavily-armed corner
of the world
could easily escalate
into nuclear confrontation.
The hour's up.
Send the helicopter.
Le's recall the Seventh Fleet.
Pull the troops out of the DMZ.
We just lost South Korea.
Our Pentagon sources are now saying
that U.S. ground troops
have been given the order
to withdraw from Korea
for the first time in 60 years.
We're also hearing reports
that the U.S.'s Seventh Fleet
has been directed to pull back
in the region.
Although unconfirmed,
this historic turn of events
seems to be motivated
by today's attack on the White House
which began
as the Prime Minister of Korea
was meeting with President Asher.
What are they doing?
Mike. We have to get Kang
and the president out
in the open and take out our best shot.
Copy that, sir.
Bravo Team is in position.
Sir, we are ready.
All units are in position.
Here come the hostages.
We count 11 targets, sir.
One of them's gotta be the president.
That's their ticket out.
Hercules Six in position.
Can you I.D. the president?
Negative.
Can you I.D. Kang?
Targets unclear.
Sir, all ground units are in position.
Do we have the go-ahead to take them?
If we're gonna go, we gotta go now, sir.
Do we have the go-ahead, sir?
No. Too risky.
They could kill the president.
Yes, sir.
It's okay.
We have a tracking device on the chopper.
Holy shit. What was that? Was that us?
Negative, negative. That wasn't us.
Though it is not confirmed yet,
President Asher
is believed to have been
among those killed
when the Blackhawk helicopter went down
in flames on the White House North Lawn.
And certainly, today's events
will be recorded in history
-as one of this country's darkest hours.
- Oh, my God.
The president's gone.
Mike?
What the hell just happened?
I'm sorry to report...
the president was on that helicopter.
And Kang?
Kang killed himself.
And all the other hostages.
Wait. This doesn't add up.
It doesn't make sense.
What doesn't make sense?
Kang would not go out like that, sir.
That's not who he is.
I think he's still in the bunker.
And he has the president.
He's gonna try and slip away.
If Kang is still on the premises
with the president,
you can't let him leave.
He won't.
Huh? Who the hell does that?
Enough!
I read your Bible, Mr. President.
It says, the wages of sin is death.
You better keep that in mind.
What are you doing?
Cerberus has been activated.
We haven't launched any missiles yet.
I don't need to launch them.
The explosive force
within each hardened silo
will detonate the missiles.
Tens of millions of Americans
will perish.
Your country will be a
cold, dark nuclear wasteland.
Now, too, America shall know
suffering and famine.
South Korean officials are saying
now that they've pulled out the reserves
and they're mobilizing additional
armored units in response...
Sir? Cerberus has been activated.
- What? -NORAD confirms.
How did it come to this?
We lost Korea and now our nukes?
- They couldn't have broken the code.
- That would be impossible.
They'd be on the bunker computer
for days to break three codes.
No, he only need to break one code.
But we haven't launched any missiles.
They're gonna detonate them
in their silos.
How many?
All of 'em.
He's just opened the gates of hell.
Time to go, Mr. President!
You really think you're gonna
get out of here alive?
The world thinks we're both dead.
And with you as insurance...
Come on, Mike.
Looks like you failed again, Mike.
Sir?
Sir, sir, look at me. Sir...
Sir.
Okay. It's gone through
and you've lost a little blood.
But I'm gonna get you outta here, okay?
Now, you know what to do.
Ben, Ben, come on!
- Cerberus. -What?
Cerberus activated.
Cerberus.
Keep that pressed in.
Sir! Ben!
You're gonna be okay.
All right.
This is Banning.
I have the president.
He's hurt, but alive.
How do I switch this fucking thing off?
- Hang on. -Deactivation code!
Find a control panel marked,
"Countermand."
Countermand.
Got it!
Flip a blue-white switch marked,
"initiate Recall."
Initiate recall.
Okay.
Deactivation sequence initiated.
Please enter abort command.
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
November. India.
Lima.
- Wait, wait. Yep. -5-Oscar-hotel.
- Oscar, hotel. -Backslash. Niner.
- Backslash. -Victor. Kilo.
- Hash-tag. -What?
- Hash-tag. -Shift 3!
Okay, fuck!
- Shift 3! -Echo.
Sierra.
- Foxtrot. -Foxtrot.
Is that it?
That's it.
Cerberus has been deactivated.
Sir. NORAD confirms...
Cerberus has been shut down.
Good.
Now get me Seoul and Pyongyang
on the line.
Are you ready, Mr. President?
All right.
Sorry about the house, sir.
It's okay. I believe it's insured.
We've lost good friends.
Family.
All good people.
- Heroes, every one of them. -Dad!
Our hearts and prayers
go out to their families.
And they will be remembered.
Nor will we forget...
those who serve out of the spotlight
to whom we owe our highest gratitude.
Our foe did not come only to destroy
our things or our people.
They came to desecrate a way of life.
To foul our beliefs,
trample our freedom.
And in this, not only did they fail...
they granted us the greatest gift.
A chance at our rebirth.
We will rise.Renewed.
Stronger and united.
This is our time...
our chance to get back
to the best of who we are.
To lead by example with the dignity,
integrity and honor
that built this country
and which will build it once again.
May God bless you.
And may God bless
the United States of America.